securenetshop.com 2014-06-30

# Securenetshop - shopping carts software, free merchant accounts, cart

## Company

### Privacy Policy

**Our Commitment To Privacy**  
SecureNetShop.com, LLC is committed to respecting and protecting the privacy of visitors to our web site as well as the privacy of our actual customers. This policy explains what information is collected from visitors and customers and how we make use of such information. The terms contained herein may be revised from time to time. To protect your interests, visit this page periodically to review the current terms of our policy.

**The Information We Collect**  
We've structured our web site so that, in general, you can visit us on the web without identifying yourself or revealing any personal information. When you visit our web site, our web server collects basic user information about you that may include your IP address, the domain from which you originated, the time you accessed our web site, and the pages from within our web site that you visit.

We may at times also use cookies, which are small pieces of information that a web site can store in a designated file on your computer. Cookies may be used to help manage sessions within various web applications, track referrals from select third parties or to tailor a specific operation to your needs, likes, and dislikes.

We may collect personally identifiable information from customers in a variety of ways, including through online forms for ordering products and services, and other instances where customers are invited to volunteer such information. While not all of the information we collect from customers is personally identifiable, it may be associated with personally identifiable information that customers provide us through our web site.

**How We Use Information**  
The basic user information collected from visitors to our web site is used to help us analyze web traffic, measure the effectiveness of our web site or our marketing, advertising and sales efforts and to improve the content of our web site.

We will occasionally send our customers emails regarding scheduled maintenance, policy changes or new features and upgrades to our services. Customers are required to receive emails of this nature due to the importance and direct impact they may have on our customers' accounts. Customers who have cancelled service with SecureNetShop.com, LLC will not receive emails of this kind.

We may also send our customers emails regarding products and services offered by SecureNetShop.com, LLC or select third parties. However, such emails will always provide recipients with the ability to opt-out of future mailings.

**Disclosure**  
We may from time to time disclose to third parties aggregate, anonymous information on our web site's traffic profile. For example, Internet advertising companies may require this data to help us better target our advertisements on our web site and/or other web sites. We may also disclose personally identifiable information when (a) it is necessary to protect the legitimate interests of SecureNetShop.com, LLC and its customers, (b) it is required to cooperate with interception orders, warrants, subpoenas or other legal process that we determine, in our sole discretion, to be valid and enforceable, (c) it is necessary to provide to a law enforcement agency when the contents are inadvertently obtained by SecureNetShop.com, LLC and appear to pertain to the commission of a crime, (d) we have reason to believe that disclosing such information is necessary to identify, make contact with, or bring legal action against a customer, should we determine, in our sole discretion, customer is causing harm or interfering with the rights or property of SecureNetShop.com, LLC, our customers, or others, or where we have a good faith belief that the law requires such disclosure. Lastly, we disclose our customers' company names, the dates in which our customers purchase or renew services and the amounts paid for such services to trusted affiliates and partners. At no time will our database of customers ever be sold to any entity for the purpose of marketing or mailing lists.

**Links and Linked Internet Web Sites**  
The SecureNetShop.com, LLC web site may provide links to web sites that are separate from the SecureNetShop.com, LLC web site. These external web sites may have their own privacy provisions in place that are different from those provisions listed in this document. We are not responsible for the collection, use or disclosure of information collected on these external web sites and we expressly disclaim any and all liability related to any collection, disclosure or use of such information. In addition, we encourage visitors to seek out and read the privacy policies of any and all sites they visit on the internet.

**Questions**  
Any questions concerning this Privacy Policy may be directed by e-mail to [sales@securenetshop.com](mailto:sales@securenetshop.com).
